Guide to the President's Office General Subject and Correspondence Files 1910-1974
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- Organizations, 1940-1972; Series 1
  - Oregon
    - Agricultural Conservation Program (Reel-folder 115.145)
    - Centennial, 1959 (Reel-folder 115.147)
    - Chest Corporation (Community Chest) (Reel-folder 115.148)
    - Education Association, 1942-1961 (Reel-folder 115.152-154)
    - Federation of Women's Club (Reel-folder 115.156)
    - Flying Farmers (Reel-folder 115.158)
    - Purebred Sheep Breeders Association (Reel-folder 115.159)
  - Oregon State Employees Association, 1955-1964 (Reel-folder 115.160)
  - Oregon Journal, 1942-1960 (Reel-folder 115.162)
  - Oregon, State of
    Boards and Commissions, Departments
    - State Institutions - Fairview Home (Reel-folder 115.192)
    - Employees Association, 1954-1958 (Reel-folder 115.193)
    - Grange (Reel-folder 115.194)
    - Legislature - Members, Correspondence with, 1950-1960 (Reel-folder 115.195)
    - Legislation - General, 1942-1958 (Reel-folder 115.196)
    - Referendum, Ballot No. 2 - Stock Amendment, 1956 (Reel-folder 115.196a)
    - Pacific Northwest Farm Council (Reel-folder 115.200)
    - Resources Development Council of Pacific Northwest Land Grant Institutions (Reel-folder 115.201)
    - United Citizens Higher Education Council of Oregon (Reel-folder 115.202)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organizations (Reel-folder 115.203)
    - Universal Military Training - Citizens Emergency Committee (Reel-folder 115.204)
  - United States Government
    - Commission on Government Security (Reel-folder 115.205)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, Office of Education - NDEA of 1958, 1958-1960 (Reel-folder 115.206-207)
    - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs, Inc. - Contract to Finance Farm Management Program in Thailand (Dr. Blanch added to Kasetsart staff) (Dr. C.V. Plath) (Dr. Gordon Sitton) (Reel-folder 115.208)
    - ICA (FOA) Kasetsart University, Bangkok, Thailand - Contract, 1960-1961 (Reel-folder 115.209-211)
    - Mutual Security Agency - Kasetsart University, Bangkok, Thailand - Cooperative Relationship - ICA (FOA) Contract, 1952-1960 (Reel-folder 116.211-222)
    - International Cooperation Administration Agreement - Servicing Participants, 1955-1960 (Reel-folder 116.223)
    - Mutual Security Agency (formally ECA) - Technical Assistance (Food Technology and Fish and Game) - MSA, FOA, ICA (Reel-folder 116.226)
    - Public Advisory Board for Mutual Security (Trade Policy Study) (Reel-folder 116.227)
    - Veterans Administration (Reel-folder 116.229)
    - Water Resources Policy Commission (Reel-folder 116.230)
  - Departments
    - Legislation - Military Training (Universal) (Reel-folder 116.244)
    - Interior Dept. - U.S. Geological Survey, Quality of Water Branch, Memo of Agreement between OSC and U.S. Geological Survey (Reel-folder 116.246)
    - Legislation - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1953-1960 (Reel-folder 116.249)
  - The Oregonian (Reel-folder 155.188)
  - Wage Price Freeze (Reel-folder 155.189)
  - "P" (Reel-folder 155.190)
  - Pacific N.W. Conference of Higher Education (Reel-folder 155.191)
  - Pacific Power and Light (Reel-folder 155.192)
  - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation (Reel-folder 155.193)
  - Portland Graduate Center (Reel-folder 155.194)
  - "R" (Reel-folder 155.195)
  - Radiation Center (Reel-folder 155.196)
  - Report of the President - OSU, 1963-1964 (Reel-folder 155.197)
  - Procedure for Calculating Attributable Costs for NDEA Fellowships (Reel-folder 155.198)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation (Reel-folder 155.199)
  - "Si" (Reel-folder 155.200)
  - Southern Pacific Company (Reel-folder 155.201)
  - Standard Oil Company (Reel-folder 155.202)
  - Student's Rights, Freedom and Responsibilities (Reel-folder 155.203)
  - "St" (Reel-folder 155.204)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America (Reel-folder 155.205)
  - "U" (Reel-folder 155.206)
  - U.S. Government
    - Agencies and Commissions, Departments: Agriculture - Civil Rights Inspections, Affirmative Action Program (Reel-folder 156.217)
    - General Departments Legislation - Correspondence (Reel-folder 157.248)
  - "W" (Reel-folder 157.249)
  - Western Association of Graduate Schools (Reel-folder 157.250)
  - Western Interstate Commission of Higher Education (Reel-folder 157.251)
  - Weyerhaeuser Timber Company (Reel-folder 157.252)
  - "Wi" (Reel-folder 157.253)
  - Willamette Basin Project Committee (Reel-folder 157.254)
  - Willamette Valley Research Council (Reel-folder 157.255)
  - Womens' Attitudes (Reel-folder 157.256)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation (Reel-folder 157.257)
  - Wyckoff (Reel-folder 157.258)
  - "XYZ" (Reel-folder 157.259)
  - "A" (Reel-folder 149.01)
  - Administrative Policies Relating to the Rights and Responsibilities of Members of the University Community and the Guarantee of their Individual Freedom (Reel-folder 149.02)
  - The American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education (Reel-folder 149.03)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1967-1972 (Reel-folder 149.04)
  - American Association of University Women, 1951-1971 (Reel-folder 149.05)
  - American Chemical Society (Reel-folder 149.06)
  - American Council on Education (Reel-folder 149.07)
  - American Legion - General (Reel-folder 149.08)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities - Executive Secretary (Reel-folder 149.09)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities - Industrial Extension (U.S. Dept. of Commerce) (Reel-folder 149.10)
  - "B" (Reel-folder 149.11)
  - Benton County Health Department (Reel-folder 149.12)
  - "Bi" (Reel-folder 149.13)
  - Biennial Budget Priorities, 1971-1972 (Reel-folder 149.14)
  - "C" (Reel-folder 149.15)
  - Campus Disturbance - BSU, 1969 (Reel-folder 149.16)
  - Charter Day Address: The Many Voices of the University (Dr. Hovland), 1964 (Reel-folder 149.17)
  - "Co" (Reel-folder 150.18)
  - College Entrance Examination Board (Reel-folder 150.19)
  - College Inns (Reel-folder 150.20)
  - Colleges and Universities
    - Colorado State University (Reel-folder 150.21)
    - General (Reel-folder 150.21a)
    - Iowa State University (Reel-folder 150.22)
    - Merrill Palmer School (Reel-folder 150.23)
    - Michigan State University (Reel-folder 150.24)
    - Montana State University (Reel-folder 150.25)
    - Reed College (Reel-folder 150.26)
    - US International University (Reel-folder 150.27)
    - University of Alaska (Reel-folder 150.28)
    - University of California, Berkeley (Reel-folder 150.29)
    - University of Colorado - Inter-University Communication of the Superior Student (Reel-folder 150.30)
    - University of Hawaii (Reel-folder 150.31)
    - University of Idaho - Salary Info Exchange, 1958 (Reel-folder 150.32)
    - University of Minnesota (Reel-folder 150.33)
    - University of Nevada (Reel-folder 150.34)
    - University of Southern California (Reel-folder 150.35)
    - University of Washington (Reel-folder 150.36)
    - University of Wyoming (Reel-folder 150.37)
    - Washington State University (Reel-folder 150.38)
    - Willamette University (Reel-folder 150.39)
    - Colleges of Oregon's Future Fund Campaign (Reel-folder 150.40)
  - Complaints - General (Reel-folder 151.41)
  - Concepts and Organizations of Graduate Center - Advisory Committee Report to the Government of Oregon (Reel-folder 151.42)
  - Continuing Education for Oregon's Colleges and Universities (Reel-folder 151.43)
  - Corvallis Chamber of Commerce (Reel-folder 151.44)
  - Corvallis - OSC Fire Protection Committee (Reel-folder 151.45)
  - Corvallis Gazette-Times (Reel-folder 151.46)
  - Corvallis - Good Samaritan Hospital (Reel-folder 151.47)
  - Corvallis - Sewer Project (Reel-folder 151.48)
  - Corvallis - Streets (Reel-folder 151.49)
  - Corvallis - Urban Renewal (Reel-folder 151.50)
  - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs Inc. (Reel-folder 151.51)
  - "D" (Reel-folder 151.52)
  - "Do" (Reel-folder 151.53)
  - "E" (Reel-folder 151.55)
  - Eugene Register Guard (Reel-folder 151.56)
  - Educational Tester Service (Reel-folder 151.57)
  - "F" (Reel-folder 151.59)
  - Inter-Institutional TV, the First Two Years (Reel-folder 151.60)
  - Ford Foundation - Faculty Fellowships (Reel-folder 151.61)
  - Ford Foundation - General (Reel-folder 151.62)
  - "G" (Reel-folder 151.63)
  - General Motors Corporation (Reel-folder 151.64)
  - Girls Residential Training Center (Reel-folder 151.65)
  - "Gr" (Reel-folder 151.66)
  - "H" (Reel-folder 151.67)
  - "He" (Reel-folder 151.68)
  - "Ho" (Reel-folder 151.69)
  - "I" (Reel-folder 151.70)
  - Institute for Behavioral Research (Reel-folder 151.71)
  - Institute of International Education (Reel-folder 151.72)
  - Institute of International Education - Annual Survey of Scholarships (Reel-folder 151.73)
  - "J" (Reel-folder 151.74)
  - "K" (Reel-folder 151.75)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation (Reel-folder 151.76)
  - "L" (Reel-folder 151.77)
  - Letter from Lieuallen - "Opinion of Attorney General about New Revenues from Buildings such as the MU" (Reel-folder 151.78)
  - "Li" (Reel-folder 151.79)
  - "M" (Reel-folder 151.80)
  - Marine Science Laboratory Administrative Plan (Reel-folder 151.81)
  - "Mc" (Reel-folder 151.82)
  - "Me" (Reel-folder 151.83)
  - "Mo" (Reel-folder 151.84)
  - "N" (Reel-folder 151.85)
  - Name of Buildings (Reel-folder 151.86)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges
    - General (Reel-folder 151.87)
    - President's Correspondence (Reel-folder 151.88)
    - President Elect (Reel-folder 151.89)
    - Task Force (Reel-folder 151.90)
  - National Association of State Universities (Reel-folder 151.91)
  - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (Reel-folder 151.92)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Reel-folder 151.93)
  - National Commission on Accrediting (Reel-folder 151.94)
  - National Commission of Accrediting - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (Reel-folder 152.95)
  - National Research Council - National Academy of Sciences (Reel-folder 152.96)
  - National Science Foundation (Reel-folder 152.97)
  - National - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Reel-folder 152.98)
  - Northwest Association of Secondary and Higher Schools (Reel-folder 152.99)
  - Northwest Association of Secondary and Higher Schools - Accreditation (Reel-folder 152.100)
  - Northwest Natural Gas (Reel-folder 152.101)
  - Northwest Scientific Association (Reel-folder 152.102)
  - Northwest Miscellaneous - Correspondence (Reel-folder 152.103)
  - "O" (Reel-folder 152.104)
  - Oregon (Reel-folder 152.105)
  - Oregon Agricultural Research Advisory Council (Reel-folder 152.106)
  - Oregon Cattleman's Association (Reel-folder 152.107)
  - Oregon Dairy Industry (Reel-folder 152.108)
  - Oregon Graduate Center (Reel-folder 152.109)
  - Oregon Museum of Science and Industry (Reel-folder 152.110)
  - Oregon State Fair (Reel-folder 152.111)
  - Oregon State Grange (Reel-folder 152.112)
  - OSC Federal Credit Union (Reel-folder 152.113)
  - Oregon, State of
    Reel-Folder numbers added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Boards and Commissions (Reel-folder 1.01)
    - Departments (Reel-folder 1.02)
    - Legislature (Reel-folder 1.03)
- Oregon State College/University, 1910-1974; Series 2
  Series 2 features 47 Sub-Series documenting groups associated with, and topics relating to Oregon State College/University. These groups and topics include: University administration; the Agricultural Experiment Station; the Forest Experiment Station; the Federal Extension Service in association with Agriculture; Institutional Services; Instructional Services, both in general and in association with the Personnel Coordinator; Libraries and Museums; Instruction, both general and in association with Schools and the Lower Division; the Physical Plant; Student Life; University administration in association with Campus Events; the Distinguished Professor Award; the Experiment Station; the Computer Center; the Physical Plant relating to the construction of buildings; Research Centers and Institutes; miscellaneous Reference File Reports; and Staff.
  - Board of Higher Curricula, 1910-1941 (Reel-folder 132.2387)
  - Budgets (1 of 2), 1945-1960 (Reel-folder 132.2388)
  - Budgets (2 of 2), 1945-1960 (Reel-folder 133.2388)
  - Federal Cooperative Extension Service, 1947-1956 (Reel-folder 133.2390)
  - Oregon State System of Higher Education - Operating Budget, 1948-1960 (Reel-folder 133.2391)
  - Memorial Union - Annual Program Report, 1955-1962 (Reel-folder 133.2393)
  - President Biennial Reports, 1939-1968 (Reel-folder 134.2393)
  - Departmental Doctoral Program - Resource Geography (Reel-folder 134.2400)
  - School of Education - International Teacher Development Program, 1963 (Reel-folder 134.2401)
  - The Next One Hundred Years in Forestry, 1959 (Reel-folder 134.2402)
  - Predicted Grades First-Term Freshman, 1963 (Reel-folder 134.2403)
  - A Summary of Current Research in Fisheries and Wildlife, 1963 (Reel-folder 134.2404)
  - Microbiology - Lab Procedure (Reel-folder 134.2405)
  - Unification, 1941-1942 (Reel-folder 134.2406)
  - Reference File Curricula (1 of 2), 1952-1961 (Reel-folder 134.2407)
  - Reference File Curricula (2 of 2), 1952-1961 (Reel-folder 135.2407)
  - Kitzhaber Reports, 1959 (Reel-folder 135.2408)
  - School of Engineering - Annual Reports - Placement Office - Sanitary Engineering, 1960-1963 (Reel-folder 135.2409)
  - Administration, 1926-1972
    - Campus Events (Reel-folder 1.01)
    - Committees (Reel-folder 1.02)
    - Councils (Reel-folder 1.03)
    - Faculty (Reel-folder 1.04)
    - Gifts and Grants (Reel-folder 1.05)
    - National Science Foundation (Reel-folder 1.06)
    - President's Office (Reel-folder 1.07)
    - Dean of Administration (Reel-folder 1.08)
    - Legislature (Reel-folder 1.09)
    - President (Reel-folder 1.10)
    - War Activities (Reel-folder 1.11)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station
    - General (1 of 3), 1940-1961 (Reel-folder 122.881)
    - General (2 of 3), 1940-1961 (Reel-folder 122.894)
    - General (3 of 3), 1940-1961 (Reel-folder 122.895)
    - Agricultural Research Foundation Report Research (Reel-folder 122.895a)
    - Cooperative Agreement between The Oregon Klamath River Commission, The California Klamath River Commission and the Oregon State Board of Higher Education - Investigation of Phytoplankton Condition in Water (Reel-folder 122.896)
    - Cooperative Agreement between County Court of Klamath County, Oregon, City of Klamath Falls, Oregon, Klamath County Chamber of Commerce and The Oregon State Board of Higher Education - Weed problems in Klamath Lake - Dr. Phinney (Reel-folder 122.897)
    - Cooperative Agreement between the U.S. Department of Interior, Bureau of Reclamation, and OSC Agriculture Experiment Station (Reel-folder 122.898)
    - Aquatic Weed Control (Reel-folder 122.899)
    - Cooperative Agreement - Insect Surveys in Oregon (Reel-folder 122.900)
    - Cooperative Agreement - Oregon State Tax Commission and OSC Agriculture Experiment Station - Study Factors for Appraisal of Agricultural Land (Reel-folder 122.901)
    - Forest Soils (Reel-folder 122.902)
    - Memo of Understanding between Monsanto Chemical Company and Agriculture Experiment Station - Evaluation of Synthetic Chemicals (Reel-folder 122.903)
  - Forest Experiment Station
    - McDonald Forest - Adair Tract (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 122.908)
    - McDonald Forest - Adair Tract (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 122.909)
    - Blodgett Tract (Reel-folder 122.910)
    - McDonald Forest, 1926-1951 (Reel-folder 122.911)
    - Adair Tract - 6200 Acres, 1947-1960 (Reel-folder 122.912)
    - Forest Research Laboratory, 1961-1963 (Reel-folder 122.913)
    - Peavy Arboretum, 1924-1941 (Reel-folder 122.914)
  - Federal Extension Service - Agricultural
    - General (Reel-folder 122.915)
    - Budget Changes, Additions, Transfers, etc. (Reel-folder 122.916)
    - Agreement - Federal Employees' group Life Insurance (Reel-folder 122.919)
    - Agreement between OSC and State Department of Education and Bureau of Indian Affairs (Reel-folder 122.920)
    - Extension Poultry Pathologist (Reel-folder 122.921)
    - Farm Labor Program (Reel-folder 122.922)
    - Finances (Reel-folder 122.923)
    - 4-H Club Program (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 122.924)
    - 4-H Club Program (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 122.925)
    - Lease with Timberland Properties, Inc., Eugene (Reel-folder 122.926)
    - Research - Dairy Products (Reel-folder 122.929)
    - Research - Oregon Tree Nut Inventory (Reel-folder 122.930)
    - Research - Locust Project in Lake and Harney Counties (Reel-folder 122.931)
    - General (1 of 4), 1947-1963 (Reel-folder 122.933)
    - General (2 of 4), 1947-1863 (Reel-folder 122.934)
    - General (3 of 4), 1947-1963 (Reel-folder 122.935)
    - General (4 of 4), 1947-1963 (Reel-folder 122.936)
  - Institutional Services
    - General (Reel-folder 5.01)
    - Civil Service (Reel-folder 5.02)
  - Instructional Services - Personnel Coordinator
    - General, 1947-1960 (Reel-folder 123.970)
    - Academic Counseling Program (Reel-folder 123.971)
    - Admissions (1 of 2), 1957-1962 (Reel-folder 123.972)
    - Admissions (2 of 2), 1957-1962 (Reel-folder 123.973)
    - Fee Remissions (Reel-folder 123.974)
    - General (Reel-folder 123.975)
    - Registrar (1 of 4) (Reel-folder 123.976)
    - Registrar (2 of 4) (Reel-folder 123.977)
    - Registrar (3 of 4) (Reel-folder 123.978)
    - Registrar (4 of 4) (Reel-folder 123.979)
  - Libraries and Museums
    - Library Dedication (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 123.980)
    - Library Dedication (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 123.981)
    - Library - General (1 of 5), 1954-1965 (Reel-folder 123.982)
    - Library - General (2 of 5), 1954-1965 (Reel-folder 123.983)
    - Library - General (3 of 5), 1954-1965 (Reel-folder 123.984)
    - Library - General (4 of 5), 1954-1965 (Reel-folder 123.985)
    - Library - General (5 of 5), 1954-1965 (Reel-folder 123.986)
    - Library - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1947-1953 (Reel-folder 123.987)
    - Library - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1947-1953 (Reel-folder 123.988)
    - Museums Budget and Transfers (Reel-folder 123.989)
    - Museum - National Capitol Miniature (Reel-folder 123.990)
  - Instruction - Schools
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 8 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - General (Reel-folder 123.991)
    - Agriculture (Reel-folder 8.01)
    - Business and Technology - Accreditation (Reel-folder 124.1014a)
    - Education (Reel-folder 8.02)
    - Engineering (Reel-folder 8.03)
    - Forestry (Reel-folder 8.04)
    - Graduate (Reel-folder 8.05)
    - Home Economics (Reel-folder 8.06)
  - Instruction - Divisions - Lower Division
    - Economics - Geography (Reel-folder 124.1058)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - Music Department (Reel-folder 124.1059)
    - Political Science (Reel-folder 124.1061)
    - Speech Department (1 of 2), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 124.1062)
    - Speech Department (2 of 2), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 124.1062a)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - Proposal for Bachelor Degrees in Divisional Majors (1 of 4), 1958-1960 (Reel-folder 124.1063)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - Proposal for Bachelor Degrees in Divisional Majors (2 of 4), 1958-1960 (Reel-folder 124.1064)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - Proposal for Bachelor Degrees in Divisional Majors (3 of 4), 1958-1960 (Reel-folder 124.1065)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - Proposal for Bachelor Degrees in Divisional Majors (4 of 4), 1958-1960 (Reel-folder 125.1065)
    - Speech Department (Reel-folder 125.1066)
  - Instruction - Schools
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 10 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - General (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 125.1067)
    - Humanities and Social Sciences - General (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 125.1068)
    - Pharmacy - General (1 of 2), 1926-1960 (Reel-folder 125.1069)
    - Pharmacy - General (2 of 2), 1926-1960 (Reel-folder 125.1070)
    - Pharmacy - Curriculum, 1961-1962 (Reel-folder 125.1070a)
    - Science (Reel-folder 10.01)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1 of 3), 1946-1948 (Reel-folder 125.1095)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (2 of 3), 1946-1948 (Reel-folder 125.1096)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (3 of 3), 1946-1948 (Reel-folder 125.1097)
  - Instruction - Divisions
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 11 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Military Science (Reel-folder 11.01)
    - NROTC (Reel-folder 11.02)
    - Physical Education (Reel-folder 11.03)
    - Barges (Reel-folder 125.1115)
    - General (1 of 2), 1948-1959 (Reel-folder 125.1116)
    - General (2 of 2), 1948-1959 (Reel-folder 125.1117)
    - Summer Sessions - General (1 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1118)
    - Summer Sessions - General (2 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1119)
    - Summer Sessions - General (3 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1120)
    - Summer Sessions - General (4 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1121)
    - Summer Sessions - General (5 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1122)
    - Summer Sessions - General (6 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1123)
    - Summer Sessions - General (7 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1124)
    - Summer Sessions - General (8 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1125)
    - Summer Sessions - General (9 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1126)
    - Summer Sessions - General (10 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1127)
    - Summer Sessions - General (11 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1128)
    - Summer Sessions - General (12 of 12), 1949-1961 (Reel-folder 125.1129)
    - Summer Sessions - Institute of Marine Biology, 1947-1951 (Reel-folder 125.1130)
    - General (1 of 3), 1949-1959 (Reel-folder 125.1132)
    - General (2 of 3), 1949-1959 (Reel-folder 125.1133)
    - General (3 of 3), 1949-1959 (Reel-folder 125.1134)
    - Property Custodian (Reel-folder 126.1135)
    - ROTC Bills (Reel-folder 126.1136)
    - Signal Corps (Reel-folder 126.1137)
  - Physical Plant
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 12 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Institutional Research (Space Utilization) (1 of 5), 1961-1967 (Reel-folder 126.1138)
    - Institutional Research (Space Utilization) (2 of 5), 1961-1967 (Reel-folder 126.1139)
    - Institutional Research (Space Utilization) (3 of 5), 1961-1967 (Reel-folder 126.1140)
    - Institutional Research (Space Utilization) (4 of 5), 1961-1967 (Reel-folder 126.1141)
    - Institutional Research (Space Utilization) (5 of 5), 1961-1967 (Reel-folder 126.1142)
    - Construction (Reel-folder 12.01)
    - Property (Reel-folder 12.02)
    - Purchases (Reel-folder 12.03)
    - Sales (Reel-folder 12.04)
    - Buildings (Reel-folder 12.05)
    - Departments (Reel-folder 12.06)
    - General Superintendent (Reel-folder 12.07)
  - Student Life - General - Campus Review (Reel-folder 129.2190)
  - Student Field Trip Survey (Reel-folder 129.2191)
  - Oregon State College Federation (Reel-folder 129.2192)
  - Student Life
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 13 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Alumni Association (Reel-folder 13.01)
    - Associated Students (Reel-folder 13.02)
    - Committees (Reel-folder 13.03)
    - Educational Funds (Reel-folder 13.04)
    - Health Service, 7/1/1947 and prior (Reel-folder 129.2236)
    - Honors Societies - Alpha Kappa Psi (Reel-folder 129.2237)
    - Associated Students - Honors Societies - Arnold Air Society (Reel-folder 129.2238)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Reel-folder 13.05)